civiltoday.com 2015-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Civil Engineering

> A cookie, also known as an HTTP cookie, web cookie, or browser cookie, is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user's web browser while the user is browsing that website.

> A web server typically sends a cookie containing a unique session identifier. The web browser will send back that session identifier with each subsequent request and shopping basket items are stored associated with a unique session identifier. Allowing users to log into a website is a frequent use of cookies.

Our site, like most other sites, uses [cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) to provide you with a more personalized and user-friendly experience. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, but then your preferences, passwords and other information will not be saved, and you may have to re-enter information to use certain features of our Site.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. These companies may use some information (such as your domain type, your IP address, about your visits to this and other Websites) in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

[Google](https://www.google.com/), one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. To find out more about [Google](https://www.google.com/) and its [DoubleClick](https://www.google.com/doubleclick/) DART cookie used to generate interest-based advertising, or to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Your use of this website without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with interest-based advertising.

We may also log IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration or to report information in aggregate form to our advertisers (e.g., how many visitors logged in to our Website). In some cases your IP address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer Internet access provider such as [AOL](http://www.aol.com/ "AOL Inc. is an American multinational mass media corporation based in New York City which develops, grows, and invests in brands and web sites.") or [Earthlink](http://www.earthlink.net/ "EarthLink is an IT services, network and communications provider headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia, US. The company serves more than 150,000 businesses and 1 million U.S. consumers"), chances are that your IP address varies each session, thus making it effectively impossible for us to use your IP address to determine who you are.

In general, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. We will disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that any applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it, or where we believe disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user.

By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Statement. If you are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Statement, you may feel free to e-mail us with questions or concerns, but your only remedy is to discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time.

Our site may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you use these links to leave our site, we do not anymore have control over that website. Such sites are not governed by this privacy statement and we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide to those sites. Exercise caution and read the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: admin (at) civiltoday (dot) com.
  *[IP]: Internet Protocol address
